Guide to the Arthur Einstein Papers, 1978-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1990-2001 and undated
  - RL10039-VHS-0052. Clarity Coverdale Fury. 1998 May 12. VHS. Park Nicollet Clinic, :30. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0053. Cliff Freeman and Partners Reel for IBM. 1993 July 6. VHS. 22 spots. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0054. CMG Communications.Undated. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0055. Cole Henderson Drake. Undated. VHS. Abita beer, Blue Cross & Blue Shield of Georgia, The Game, Organ Donation, Garber Motors, Atlanta Gas & Light. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0056. Compton Partners/Saatchi & Saatchi. 1995 Oct. 31. VHS. Volunteers of America spots. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0057. Compton Partners/Saatchi & Saatchi. 1995 Sept. 15. VHS. Volunteers of America spots. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0058. Core. Undated. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0059. Cox Group Agency B Reel. Undated. VHS. Running time 8:00. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0060. Cox Group Agency Showreel. Undated. VHS. Running time 8:00. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0061. Cranford Johnson Robinson Woods. Undated. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0062. Cranford Johnson Robinson Woods. Undated. VHS. Agency video, A Really Good Idea! (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0063. Crispin Porter Bogusky. Undated. VHS. Time Magazine spots. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0064. Crispin Porter Bogusky. Undated. VHS. Longhorn Steakhouse, :30. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0065. Crispin Porter Bogusky. 2001 June 27. VHS. Florida Department of Health spots, 5:00. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0066. Crispin Porter Bogusky agency reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0067. D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, Best of DMB&B Worldwide. 1995 June. VHS. Aleve, Lockheed, Crest, TWA, Dow, Southwest Bell, Cadillac, Crystal Light, Amoco, Blockbuster, Scope, Moneygram, Pampers, Budweiser, Philips, ATC, Texaco, Water Authority, Umbro, UK Transportation, Mars, Bavaria, Johnny Walker, Pi Wei Li, Fanta, Copec, Heliar. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0068. D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, Some Creative Thoughts from DMB&B. 1999 July. VHS. Norelco, Pontiac, Cadillac, SBC, ATC, Twix, Street.com, Crest, PDFA,. Swatch, Bon Aqua, Philishave. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0069. D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, The Latest from DMB&B. 1994 Aug. VHS. Crystal Light, Clearasil, General Motors, Cadillac, Budweiser, Freihofer's, Lawman Jeans, Blockbuster, Michelob, Pontiac, Whirlpool, Amoco, Philishave, Baskin Robbins, ProPlayer. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0070. D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, Max 8: DMB&B Creative Achievement Awards. Undated. VHS. Pontiac, Scope, Crest, Baskin-Robbins, Skittles, Toyota, Utterly Butterly, Fiat, M-Tel Cellular, Bon Aqua, Laphroaig, Pollini, Bell, Laciate Tetrapak, Dutch Rail, Folha Norte, Banco America do Sol, Rio Sul, Philips, Ostrich Meat and Marketing, Coffee Connection, Bonds Cottontails, Bonds Infantwear, Johnson Wax, Selsun Shampoo. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0071. D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, The Latest and Greatest. 1997 Oct.VHS. Coca-Cola, Norelco, Scope, Twix, Southwestern Bell, Gateway, Bonneville, Grand Prix, Crest, Milky Way, Vick's, Spectrum, TWA, Blue Cross, LG Group, LaCoste, Whiskas, Rio Sul, Rover Car, Whirlpool, Kaopectate, Philips, Drug Free Brazil, Sing Tao Post, Hippodromo, Umbro, Scholl's, Tuborg, Swatch, Dutch Rail, Littlewoods Pools. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0072. D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, The Latest from DMB&B. Undated. VHS. Crystal Light, Budweiser, General Motors, Whirlpool, Pontiac, Freihofer's, Clearasil, Australian Toasted Biscuits, Cadillac, Baskin-Robbins. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0073. Dcode Creative Reel. Undated. VHS. Sprite, Diet Coke, U.S. Virgin Islands Tourism, Teen People, New York Sports Club, Heineken, Amstel Light, Kemper Insurance. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0074. DDB Needham, Creative Reel, radio and television. Undated. VHS. New York Lottery, CIGNA, Digital Equipment, MetroStars, Frito-Lay, Mobil, Michelin, Bud Light, Bermuda, North Shore Animal League (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0075. DDB Needham, Cannes winners (TV). 1993. VHS. Volkswagen, Centraal Beheer, Audi, TV Channel, New York State Lottery, Barclaycard, Soya Light, Trex, Lynx Golf Club. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0076. DDB Needham Worldwide. Undated. VHS. Bermuda, Bud Light, Twizzlers, Travel Channel, Clean and Clear, NSAL, MetroStars, NYSL, Dial, WFL, Northern, Michelin, Brawny. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0077. DDB Needham, Selected Cannes Winners 1992-1994. 1994. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0078. DDB Needham. Undated. VHS. Volunteers of America, 6:05. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0079. Dentsu (Japan), Television. 1991 Mar.VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0080. Deutsch. Undated. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0081. DiMark, The Brand of Winning Direct. Undated. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0082. DiMassimo. Undated. VHS. Ten spots. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0083. Don Coleman and Associates Presentation Reel. 1993 Mar. 11. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0084. Doremus. Undated. VHS. Morgan Stanley Webs, 1:30. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0085. Doremus. 1998 Sept. 18. VHS. ITT Industries, :30. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0086. Doremus. Undated. VHS. ACE Group, Setting Your Future Free. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0087. Doremus. Undated. VHS. Multex.com. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0088. Doyle Advertising Introduction. 1993 Mar. 9. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0089. Dugan Valva Contess (DVC) Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. Running time 2:30. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0090. Earle Palmer Brown Creative Credentials. 1991 June 6.VHS. Isuzu, 5:50. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0091. Edelman Public Relations Worldwide, Annual Report. 1994. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0092. ELAN (European Local Agency Network), Show Reel. 1994. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0093. Elgin DDB Agency Reel. 1998 Dec. 15.VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0094. ESS Demo Reel. 1998. VHS. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0095. E (Enterprisecs) compilation reel. 1998 Apr. VHS. Nine spots. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0096. Fallon McElligott agency reel. 1992 Aug. 19. VHS. Time, Hush Puppies, Lee Jeans, Nature's Course, Timex, Ralston Purina, Bassett Walker, Violence Against Women, Northwest Airlines, Penn. (Box AV3)
  - RL10039-VHS-0097. E James White Communications company Demo Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0098. Fast Shoes (T-Bone Films). 1996. VHS. Running time 40:00 (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0099. FGI Integrated Marketing. Undated. VHS. TCI Cable, CCB, Maola Milk, Super Pretzel, Cellular One, Kidde, News and Observer. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0100. Fitch Presentation Reel. 1998 Mar. 26. VHS. Running time 5:42. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0101. Fitzgerald and Company. Undated. VHS. Haverty's, TVA, Jerzee's, Boars Head Inn, Hawks, PacTel, Air Touch, NBAF, 6:00. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0102. Fletcher Martin Associates. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0103. Focus Agency, Some Examples of Our Work. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0104. Focus Agency, Some Examples of Our Recent Work. 1998 Mar. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0105. Focus Agency, Some Examples of Our Work. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0106. Follis Advertising Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0107. Foote Cone & Belding San Francisco, Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. MTV, SF MOMA, Sega, Fox Sports, Slates, Seagate, Coors, AT&T, Zima. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0108. Foote Cone & Belding San Francisco, Television reel. 1996. VHS. Keds, Excite. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0109. Foote Cone & Belding San Francisco, Television Credentials Reel. 1996. VHS. Levi Strauss, Coors, Janus Funds, Gallo, Pacific Bell, Armor All, Teledyne, Disney Interactive, Zima. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0110. Foote Cone & Belding (FCB/Lieber Katz Partners) Presentation Reel. 1995 Oct. VHS. Jamaica, Oreo, LifeSavers, Milk-Bone, Citibank, Snackwells, V-8, Fila, Shredded Wheat, Northwest Airlines, AT&T. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0111. Forman End Dolleck Advertising. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0112. Friedland Jacobs Communications (FJC) Agency Reel. 1997 Jan. VHS. ABC/Carsey Werner, Warner Bros., Turner Program Services, Dreamworks SKG, NBC, Worldvision, King World, 20th Television, CBS, WTVJ-TV, WCAU-TV, New World. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0113. Frierson Mee + Kraft (fm+k) short version. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0114. Fox Pavlika & Partners. Undated. VHS. Berger Mutual Funds. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0115. Frankel & Company. Undated. VHS. Tales of Two Cities, 5:24. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0116. Galaspy & Lobel Advertising Demo Reel. 1993 Apr.VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0117. Gardner, Geary, Coll & Young (GGC&Y) agency reel. Undated. VHS. Delta Dental, Enabl, Lombard, Power Wheels, Fetzer Vineyards, State Fund, California Gold. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0118. Gigante Vaz & Partners. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0119. Gigante Vaz & Partners. Undated. VHS. Aiwa America, 1:30. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0120. Gigante Vaz & Partners. Undated. VHS. Aiwa America, 1:30. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0121. Gillespie--The Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0122. Gillespie--The Reel. Undated. VHS. Time Warner, Port Authority, Sierra Anti-Freeze, Seagram's Coolers, ITT Corporate, Heineken, Taos Aperitif. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0123. Glennon Case History Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0124. Goldsmith/Jeffrey Agency Reel. 1996 Spring.VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0125. Goodby, Berlin & Silverstein Agency Reel. 1993 Nov. 1. VHS. San Francisco Examiner, NBA, Isuzu, Norwegian Cruise Line, Librex Computers, Chevy's Mexican Restaurants, Sega, Oakland SPCA, Northern California Honda, Partnership for a Drug-Free America, Blossom Hill Wine, Royal Viking Cruise Line, 8:30. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0126. Gotham Incorporated, A Message from Stone Roberts. 1999 Feb. 5.VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0127. Ground Zero. 1994 June.VHS. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0128. Ground Zero. 1994 June.VHS. Porsche spots. (Box AV4)
  - RL10039-VHS-0129. Grupo Cuatro Publicidad Agency reel. Undated. VHS. Snapple, Gatorade, Quaker Oatmeal, Cap'n Crunch, Wolf Brand Chili. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0130. Grybauskas Beatrice. 1997 July 16.VHS. Jose Cuervo, Playboy, Tommy Hilfiger. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0131. GSD&M (Gurasich Spence Darilek & McClure) Demo Reel for Compaq. 1991 Sept. 27. VHS. Coors, Wal-Mart, Don't Mess with Texas, PGA Tour, Southwest Airlines, Traffic Safety PSA. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0132. GSD&M (Gurasich Spence Darilek & McClure) Idea City. Undated. VHS. Rock the Vote, Southwest Airlines, Doubletree Hotels, Wal-Mart, Pennzoil, Fossil, Texas Tourism, Steel Alliance, Fannie Mae, RC Cola, PGA. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0133. Hadeler Sullivan Ewing Television and Radio. 1996. VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0134. Harris Drury Cohen. 2000 Jan. 26. VHS. This.com spot, :30. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0135. Harris Drury Cohen Agency Demo Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0136. Harris Drury Cohen. Undated. VHS. Del Monte television. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0137. Harris Drury Cohen. Undated. VHS. CLIA: You Haven't Lived Until You've Cruised. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0138. Harris Drury Cohen. Undated. VHS. Sea-Doo, Everybody's Doing It. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0139. Harris Drury Cohen Agency Reel. 1995. VHS. Atlantis, Sea Doo, Partnership for a Drug Free America, Value Rent-A-Car. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0140. Harris Drury Cohen. Undated. VHS. TJ Cinnamon spots. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0141. Harris Drury Cohen. Undated. VHS. Wyndham television. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0142. Heater-Easdon. Undated. VHS. Tobacco Free spots, 3:00. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0143. Herring Newman. Undated. VHS. Partnership for a Drug Free America spots. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0144. Hill, Holliday Television Creative for IBM. Undated. VHS. Spalding, Hancock, CDF, Infiniti, Reebok, Rolling Rock, Lottery, Wang, ITB, 6:00. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0145. Hill/Holliday. 1998 Apr.VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0146. Houston Effler Hampel & Stefanides, IBM PC Presentation Reel. 1993 July 1.VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0147. Ingalls, The Work. Undated. VHS. MSPCA, Price Chopper, Citizens Bank, T.J. Maxx. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0148. Institute of Canadian Advertising. 1998. VHS. Incredible Canadian Agencies, 28 spots. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0149. Institute of Canadian Advertising. Undated. VHS. Push the Boundaries: A Presentation of Canadian Advertising, 29 spots. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0150. J. Walter Thompson (JWT), Reel prepared for IBM. 1993 July 6. VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0151. J. Walter Thompson (JWT), Undated. VHS. Turning Home Runs into Grand Slams: The Role of PR at JWT. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0152. Jerry & Ketchum. 1995 Nov. 29. VHS. Bankers Trust Company spots. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0153. Joe & Sam Advertising General Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0154. Kaplan Thaler Group. Undated. VHS. AFLAC, Herbal Essences, American Red Cross, Aussie Kids, Parmalat Milk. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0155. Katz Dochtemann & Epstein (KD&E) Presentation Reel. 1993 Nov.VHS. Ford Truck, NBO, Her New York, HBO, Chestnut Ridge Raquet Club, Republic Bank, Thunderbird, Kodak. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0156. Katz Dochtemann & Epstein (KD&E) Presentation Reel. 1993 Nov.VHS. Ford Truck, NBO, Her New York, HBO, Chestnut Ridge Raquet Club, Republic Bank, Thunderbird, Kodak. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0157. Kerker.Undated. VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0158. Kirshenbaum Bond and Partners Broadcast Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0159. Kirshenbaum Bond and Partners Broadcast Reel. Undated. VHS. Snapple, Keds, Pittsburgh Brewing, Citibank Aadvantage, Quick & Reilly, NY Post, Newberger & Berman, Moet & Chandon. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0160. Kirshenbaum Bond and Partners Chanel Reel. 1993 Nov. 12.VHS. Revlon, Sunbeam, Huffman Koos, Pittsburgh Brewing, Quick & Reily, Snapple, Thom McAn, Isotoner. (Box AV5)
  - RL10039-VHS-0161. Korey Kay & Partners. Undated. VHS. Outsmarting the Outspenders. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0162. Korey Kay & Partners. Undated. VHS. Outsmarting the Outspenders. Includes Tri-Honda, Virgin Atlantic Airways, BayBank, NYCE, Members Only, MTA. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0163. Lawrence McCarthy Showreel. Undated. VHS. British Telecom, Safeway, Heinz, Tuborg, Butter Information Council, Sunblest Bread, National Savings. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0164. Leibler-Bronfman Lubalin sample reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0165. Leo Burnett Agency Reel. 1993 Aug. 4. VHS. Creative from Bud Watts' and Bob Welke's Groups. Includes United Airlines, Sony, Procter & Gamble (Cheer, Noxzema, Pepto Bismol), Oldsmobile, Unocal 76, Amore Cat Food, 19:30. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0166. Leo Burnett University Reel, 1994-1995. 1995. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0167. Leo Burnett Agency Reel. 1993 Nov. 12. VHS. McDonald's, Beef Industry Council, Heinz, Kellogg's, Oldsmobile, Tropicana, Seven-Up, Allstate, Nintendo, United Airlines, Prell, 10:00. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0168. Link Agency Television, Strategic Planning, Radio. Undated. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0169. Littlefield Broadcast Reel. 1999. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0170. Lord Dentsu & Partners. Undated. VHS. Suzuki, Best Western, Poland Spring, Kraft, Countrywide, Sears, NYNEX, Radio Shack. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0171. Lord Dentsu & Partners Agency Reel. 1993 July 6. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0172. Mad Dogs & Englishmen Agency Reel 1.0. Undated. VHS. Mill Creek, Moviefone, Road Runner, Yoo-Hoo, Time Warner Cable, Gay Financial Network, Kenneth Cole. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0173. Mad Dogs & Englishmen Yoo-Hoo Television Campaign. Undated. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0174. Margeotes Fertitta & Weiss (MF&W) Agency Reel. 1993 July 6. VHS. General Foods Cappio, Start, 2:45. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0175. Margeotes Fertitta & Weiss (MF&W) Agency Reel. 1993 nov. 9. VHS. American Standard, Monet, New York Newsday, CBS, General Foods Cappio, Swiss Army, Start. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0176. Margeotes Fertitta & Weiss (MF&W) Creative Sample Reel. 1998 Aug. 4. VHS. Partnership for a Drug Free America, MediaOne Express, McGraw-Hill, Jet-Dry, NFL Enterprises. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0177. Marshall Jaccoma Mitchell advertising. Undated. VHS. Ten spots. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0178. Marsteller Advertising Spots Compilation. 1996 May 1. VHS. Includes Eli Lilly, American Red Cross, Genentech/American Heart Association, Andersen Consulting. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0179. Martin Agency, The New Stuff. 1997 Oct. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0180. Martin/Williams, Top 12 Commercials. 1997. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0181. Martin/Williams. Undated. VHS. The Secret to the Most Successful Grand Opening in History (Target case history). (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0182. Martin/Williams, Top 10 Commercials. 1996. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0183. Martin/Williams, Here's the Other 1%, Retail sample reel. Undated. VHS. Target, Marshall Field's, Hudson's, Dayton's, Mervyn's, Play It Again Sports. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0184. Martin/Williams, Top 10 Commercials. 1995. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0185. McAdams Consumer Healthcare Advertising. Undated. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0186. McCaffrey and McCall, Television Creative 1990-1991. 1991. VHS. Mercedes-Benz, Puerto Rico Tourism, Longevity Magazine. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0187. McCaffrey and McCall, An Introduction. Undated. VHS. Mercedes-Benz, Tiffany & Co., Longevity Magazine, Sudafed, Bacardi Breezer. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0188. McKinney & Silver Agency Reel. 1999 Jan. 18. VHS. Audi, Royal Caribbean International, Governor's Mentor, MAP Mobile, Karastan. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0189. McKinney & Silver Summer Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0190. Merkley Newman Harty. Undated. VHS. ABC, Straight Talk on Drugs PSAs. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0191. Messner Vetere Berger Carey Schmetterer. Undated. VHS. Volvo infomercial, It Happens Every Second, 28:30. (Box AV6)
  - RL10039-VHS-0192. Messner Vetere Berger Carey Schmetterer. 1991 Sept. 27. VHS. Volvo, MCI, NASDAQ. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0193. Messner Vetere Berger Carey Schmetterer, Agency Year One Television Reel. 1991. VHS. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0194. Meyer & Wallis. Undated. VHS. Louie spots, 1:30. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0195. Moffatt/Rosenthal Television. 1998 Oct. 1. VHS. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0196. Mullen. Undated. VHS. Monster.com, Cozone.com. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0197. Mullen. Undated. VHS. Monster.com. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0198. Mullen. Undated. VHS. Cozone.com spots. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0199. Mullen. Undated. VHS. General Motors spots. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0200. Mullen. 1993. VHS. Timberland television. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0201. Muse Cordera Chen. 1998. VHS. Hispanic Agency of the Year (AAAA), 7 spots. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0202. New York Creatives Advertising Partners, Reel 9. Undated. VHS. R.J. Forbes, Campbell's, Carmax, White Mountain, Amtrak, Friendly's Ice Cream, Gallo, Showtime, La Yogurt, Dunkin' Donuts. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0203. Neiman Group, Agency Reel with Consumer Sports. 2000 Mar. VHS. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0204. Non-Verbal Commercials. Undated. VHS. Barilla, Roth Handle, Bank Leumi, Trygg Hansa, Heinz Ketchup, National Hi-Top, Levi's, Dentype, Luchetti, Cebolitos, IDS, National Westminster (NatWest). (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0205. North Castle Partners, Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0206. Oasis, agency reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0207. Ogilvy & Mather. Undated. VHS. Compaq and Ogilvy & Mather. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0208. Ogilvy & Mather, Television Commercials 1990-1991. 1991. VHS. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0209. Parrish Wichersham & Partners. Undated. VHS. Bose, Childreach, Christian Science Monitor, 3:00. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0210. Partners & Shevack, Presentation reel. Undated. VHS. Cambridge, NatWest, Mead, Scotts, Adidas, MLB, Franklin. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0211. Pavlika+Chinnic Direct, Our Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. Starpower, NFL Sunday Ticket, Mony Group, Ameritech, MediaOne Express. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0212. Pedone & Partners. Undated. VHS. Take a Look at Our Latest Work for 1-800-flowers.com. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0213. Pedone & Partners. 2001 June. VHS. Legal Aid Society television advertising. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0214. Pedone & Partners jagency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0215. Perich Partners, Ltd., Television and Radio. Undated. VHS. 13 spots. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0216. Periscope. 2001. VHS. Arctic Cat ATV Campaign. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0217. Periscope. Undated. VHS. Metro Transit Driver Recruitment Campaign. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0218. Publicis. Undated. VHS. BMW, Lancome, Cellular One, Club Med, Ericsson, Harp, Renault, TXU, Coca-Cola, Talens, Whirlpool, SNET. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0219. Ray Hirschman, The Reel. Undated. VHS. Alka-Seltzer, Taos, ITT, Seagram's, Mounds, Heineken, Sheraton, Canada Dry. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0220. R&D, Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. 94.5 The Edge, Hummer, Lombardo, American Spirit, Weinhard, Motel 6. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0221. RBT/Strum (renamed Star Group in 1998), Broadcast Television and Radio Spots. 1997 Nov. 12. VHS. Mediagroup, Danzeisen & Quigley, MAX 95.7-FM, N.J. Transit, Primestar, New Jersey Lottery, St. Christopher's Hospital. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0222. Richards Group. Undated. VHS. Henry Weinhard, Home Depot, Kaepa, Pergo, Hummer, EyeMasters, Texas Dept. of Health, Maxfli, Texas Rangers, Motel 6, Boar's Head, American Spirit, Rainier Beer, AlphaGraphics. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0223. Rockett, Burkhead & Winslow. Undated. VHS. Special Olympics, Glaxo Wellcome, Duke Healthcare System, Target, Carolina Hurricanes, Rich Seapak, Fleer/Skybox. (Box AV7)
  - RL10039-VHS-0224. Ron Foth Advertising, Agency Creative Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0225. Rubin Postaer and Associates. Undated. VHS. American Honda Motor Co., ARCO, Fidelity Federal Bank, am/pm, American Century Investments, Los Angeles Kings. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0226. Ryan Drossman & Partners. 1999 May 27. VHS. Church & Dwight, Arm & Hammer spots. :30. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0227. Ryan Drossman & Partners Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0228. Ryan Drossman & Partners Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0229. Saatchi & Saatchi Advertising. Undated. VHS. Delta Air Lines. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0230. Saatchi & Saatchi Advertising. Undated. VHS. Hewlett-Packard, Paine Webber, Toyota, Cheerios, Tide, Pepperidge Farm, DuPont, Reynolds, Bell Atlantic, Playtex, Drug Free America, Kix, Paramount Parks, String Thing, Reese's, Sony, Gushers, Mylanta, Tylenol, Pepsid AC. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0231. Saatchi & Saatchi Advertising. Undated. VHS. Bell Atlantic spots, 3:30. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0232. Saatchi & Saatchi Advertising. Undated. VHS. The Saatchi & Saatchi Vision, Kevin Roberts CEO. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0233. Sam Albert's Performance. Undated. VHS. Trumph of the Nerds. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0234. Sawyer Riley Compton, Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0235. SBC Advertising. Undated. VHS. Big Ideas that Build Business. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0236. SBC Advertising Courtship Marketing, Agency Broadcast Reel. Undated. VHS. Love 'Em or Lose 'Em. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0237. SBC Advertising. Undated. VHS. Big Ideas that Build Business. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0238. Scheyer/SF, Television and Radio. Undated. VHS. Mill Valley Film Festival, Toyota, Pier 39, Little Brothers, Florence Crittenton, Galileo, Capcom, Intiut/Quickbooks, Computerland, 10:00. (Box AV8)
  - RL10039-VHS-0239. Schupp Company, Agency Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV8)